#### Contact

melissac.long@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/melissa-long-rn-msn-fnp-bc-6271675a (LinkedIn) www.vanderbilthealth.com/heart/51094 (Company) twitter.com/vumcvalve (Company) twitter.com/Melissa\_C\_Long (Personal)

### Top Skills

Cardiology
Program Development
Clinical Research

# Melissa Long RN, MSN, FNP-BC

Structural Heart & Valve Program Coordinator at Vanderbilt University Medical Center

Nashville, Tennessee

## Summary

I work with our multidisciplinary group of valve specialists providing expert care and personalized treatment plans for patients with valve disease. Interested in program growth and development, research, marketing, and process improvement. In pursuit of wholehearted living.

## Experience

Vanderbilt University Medical Center 11 years 7 months

Structural Heart & Valve Program Coordinator March 2018 - Present (2 years 5 months) Nashville, TN

Cardiac Nurse Practitioner
June 2014 - Present (6 years 2 months)
Interventional Cardiology & Structural Heart Disease

#### Registered Nurse

January 2009 - June 2014 (5 years 6 months)

Greater Nashville Area, TN

Cardiac Cath Lab: Jan 2012-2014

Cardiovascular Intensive Care: Jan 2009-Dec 2011

## Education

**Belmont University** 

Master's degree, Family Practice Nurse/Nursing · (2010 - 2013)

Western Kentucky University

BSN, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse (2004 - 2008)